Ah
This is awful
Yeah, it's like a tornado and a battalion came through
It's far worse than what was reported to headquarters. We'd better quicken our pace and find Lieutenant Havoc
What's the matter Al you forget how to walk in a straight line? Stop bumping into me. Sorry these
Smoky places give me the creeps
I can't believe you got the heebie-jeebies Al you're a suit of armor
Look at the lieutenant walking all bravely up there leading the way and she's just a girl
I didn't mean to insult you in any way. I swear. I just meant
Oh
We surrounded why can't they make all this noise when they're hiding no choice boys get ready for a fight