Ah! Ah!
That's him! The guy we saw!
Yeah, from Resembool.
So, you're the one who did this to the village, aren't you?
Were you trying to do the same thing to Resembool, too?
What is your purpose for all of this?
What was that transmutation circle for?
I had a feeling we'd meet again someday.
Damn it, pal. You got a bad habit of being cryptic!
No, wait!
No circles. Impressive, young alchemist.
Interesting. You have the same eyes.
Brother!
You should have realized you have no right to stop me.
Crowley!
That's you, isn't it?
I knew it!
There could be no mistaking you!
Don't you recognize me? It's me! It's Arlen!
I can't believe this!
Crowley?
No.
The Arlen I know is not a doddering old fool like you.
What do you mean? You're talking nonsense!
How many years do you think it's been?
How can you still look so young?
What happened to you?
Crowley!
There he goes again. He just melted away.
You're safe now, Lieutenant Havoc.
So how are you faring after all of that?
You all right?
Does it look like I'm all right?
Do me a favor and tell the Colonel to double my salary, will you?
I mean, for God's sake!
How come no one ever tells me how dangerous these missions are gonna be?