What's up with these guys?
Did the whole town get up on the wrong side of the bed?
It looks like they're guarding the ruins.
Keep in mind, this is an important relic to them.
They might think we're grave robbers or something.
Okay, listen, we're good, clean-cut boys and girls.
You got it?
Now, if you'll just let us through.
I said, we're not here to loot your crappy old graves, all right?
That didn't work.
Hold on.
Something's not quite right here.
You don't think there could be that many of them?
I don't know.
Their form is starting to ring a bell.
Golems!
Why do they have to show up wherever we go?
We'd better retreat for now.
Seriously, what are a bunch of golems doing in this place?
You're asking the wrong guy!
Hey, tell your friends they've got to run.
The streets are about to be flooded with real nasty creatures and with beady eyes.
Is this the place where the science said always a golden town?
This place has been in ruins for centuries.
I knew something wasn't right.
But now we've got the whole thing figured out, don't we?
Yeah, that's right.
Tell them these things won't pass next time, Grandpa.
I'm sorry.