What now?
I'm not sure.
Damn, there's just too many of these things.
Are you having difficulties, Edward Elric?
How can one struggle against a lumbering enemy whose only strength is in its numbers?
Behold, these deformations.
Behold! The marriage of alchemy and physical strength.
Passed down the Armstrong line for generations.
Witness the art of alchemy combined with physical strength!
That wasn't too much, was it?
It's so hard holding yourself back in battle when you're fighting brainless drones.
Colonel.
My sincerest apologies, Lieutenant. We did mean to arrive a little earlier.
Geez, don't you guys know how to come onto a scene?
Without making a scene, you're so attention-starved.
Right. You knew I'd have to show my face sometime.
So how have things been going, Fullmetal?
Looks like this was a close call. Guess that means you owe me one.
I don't owe you anything. These golems couldn't get an inch on...
And now, you owe me two.
If you're my backup, then back me up!
That's funny. But I'm not here for backup, Fullmetal.
You've fought bravely enough. Now you can leave it in the hands of the state.