Let's do it.
Yeah.
It's over.
Come on, hurry up.
Few more minutes of this and we're history.
What is this?
It looks like Edward has intervened here.
I'd say so.
Way to go, Fullmetal.
You left that circle on the platform.
The last shred of decency you had as a human being, Crowley.
What's this, an earthquake?
It's bad, that's what it is.
We gotta get out, fast.
Mr. Glossner, what are you doing?
We have to run.
Just go, boys.
I think I'll stay here a while.
What are you, insane?
If you stay here, you'll be crushed along with the rest of these ruins.
That's fine by me.
You boys are still young, so you won't understand it.
But I'm going to share my fate with Crowley and Elma.
My last mission in life has been finished.
I've got no reason to live any longer.
Crowley, Elma, and me, we were always together, through everything.
I think it's only fitting I take my rest with them, too.
Last mission, always together?
My ass!
None of that crap gives you a reason to die here?
It doesn't matter.
I've made up my mind.
Thanks, Mr. Fullmetal Alchemist, for getting me here.
All right, that's it.
I want to sleep well tonight, and I'm not going to have you on my conscience.
Hey, Al.
Way ahead of you.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You better stop squirming, or else I'll make you ride inside.
You can't do this!
All right, let's run.
Put me down!
I want to stay!
I have to!
And so it ends, a familiar story in these parts.
One man's obsession to bring back from the dead the one he loves the most.
A tragic end, indeed.
Ed, what are you thinking right now?
Probably the same thing that you're thinking, Al.
Ed!