I-I don't know. I hope you don't mind if I take you to the cell.
Oh, what a lovely trip.
Don't you think?
Bye, honey.
Well, we made it.
I guess we're finally on our way to Central now.
Right, the library.
I nearly forgot. That was quite the detour.
Well, it would be very disingenuous of me not to say well done, Edward Elric.
Excellent job.
Yeah, well, that's the great thing about working hard.
You make everybody's lives easier and still nobody shows up to wave you goodbye.
Come now. You know everyone at East Headquarters is busy.
By the way, I thought you'd be interested to know that Mr. Glossner character you spent time with has returned to Siam-Sid.
What? He went back?
Apparently the man has adamant that he's going to spend the rest of his life there.
Even though civilians aren't allowed on the premises because there's still so much the state wants to look into.
Are you thinking about Crowley again?
I was. I mean, maybe we're no different than he was.
If we'd taken one wrong step, all of this could have happened to us.
We won't do that.
I'm telling you right now, that's one wrong step we're never going to take.
We'd never sacrifice life just for our own selfish gains to get an arm or a body that we want.
Yeah.
Sacrificing somebody's entire life only because you want to be happy, that can never be called equivalent exchange.
So we'll just have to keep looking for the real answer out there.
What is it, Major?
Nothing to worry about.
It just seems that you've grown tremendously through this incident, Edward Elric.
I've grown? You mean you really think I got taller?
That's great!